cleantech.com 2019-07-03

# Privacy Policy | Cleantech Group

**PRIVACY AND PERSONAL DATA**

The guidelines below detail the data protection policy of Cleantech Group regarding personal data.

Cleantech Group strives for transparency and takes very seriously the confidentiality of personal information and data provided by you.

By providing your personal information and data, you consent to the use, analysis and, where applicable, disclosure of such information by us according to the terms and conditions described herewith.

  1. GENERAL INFORMATION

Cleantech Group may collect personal data via its website from, among other things, requests to create a user account or requests to subscribe to our newsletter and other mailings. Cleantech Group will also collect personal information if you subscribe to our premium services, or if you register for Cleantech Group events.

If you communicate with us by phone, email, post messages to any of our social media groups, forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.

Personal Information may include: (1) Contact Data (such as your name, company name, title, phone number, mailing and email addresses); (2) Traffic Data (such as your IP address, domain server, type of computer, type of web browser, search history and page view history).

All personal data that you are transmitting to Cleantech Group for the benefit of services provided in this website will be treated according to the [Online Privacy Protection Act of 2003 – Online Privacy Protection Act of 2003 – California Business and Professions Code sections 22575-22579](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode=BPC&division=8.&title=&part=&chapter=22.&article=) and [The General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) effective from May 25, 2018](https://www.eugdpr.org/the-regulation.html).

  2. RIGHT TO ACCESS, CORRECT AND DELETE DATA AND TO OBJECT TO DATA PROCESSING

All mailings from us will provide a link to allow you to unsubscribe.

Beyond unsubscribing, you are also entitled to access, correct and delete personal data which relates to you, and to object to the processing of such data. You may exercise this right at any time by contacting us via the following methods:

  * Complete our [contact form](http://info.cleantech.com/ContactUs.html) on our website
  * Send an email to: [helpdesk@cleantech.com](mailto:helpdesk@cleantech.com)
  * Write to: Cleantech Group, 1714 Franklin St, 100-286, Oakland CA 94612, United States

  3. MANAGEMENT OF PERSONAL DATA BY THE COMPANY

3.1 Purpose of data collection

Cleantech Group collects your personal data via its website for the following purposes only:

  * managing subscriptions to our research services, our newsletter and press releases
  * managing attendance at and/or participation in our international events series
  * sending documents requested via the website
  * sending periodic notifications of our events series and releases of our research, and occasional promotional materials of relevance, given your past interactions with us
  * billing and account management

3.2 Retention of data

We retain data collected for the purposes of managing premium subscriptions and active user accounts for a minimum of the term of service. Otherwise, data may be retained indefinitely unless you request that we delete it. Once we receive a data deletion request, we will undertake to delete all data within one week of the request.

3.3 Data recipients

Cleantech Group is the recipient of the data. We have security and privacy measures in place to ensure an adequate level of data protection. We do not in the normal course of business share your data with third parties. Cleantech Group will only send your personal data to a third party if:

  * you have given us your prior approval to share such information,
  * Cleantech Group must share such information with third parties to provide a service you have requested, or
  * Cleantech Group is required by a judicial authority or any other administrative authority to provide such information.

3.4 Data security and privacy

Cleantech Group has made every effort to put in place suitable precautions to safeguard the security and privacy of personal data, and to prevent it from being altered, corrupted, destroyed or accessed by unauthorized third parties.

However, the company does not control every risk related to the use of the Internet, and therefore warns visitors of the potential risks involved in the functioning and use of the Internet.

  4. COOKIES

When you visit our company website, a cookie may be automatically installed and temporarily saved in your computer’s memory or on its hard disk to make it easier for you to navigate around our site and to save your password. Cookies do not enable us to identify you, but are used to record information about the pages you have viewed on our website, the date and time of your visit to the site, etc.

You can disable cookies in your web browser. However, this will disable all cookies used by your browser, including those from other websites, which may cause certain settings or information to be altered or lost. Disabling cookies may change your browsing experience on our website or may make navigating around the site more difficult.

  5. HOW WE RESPOND TO DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS (DNT)

This site does not respond to DNT signals. If we are providing services to you, such as subscriptions or user accounts, we will track page views and sign-in logs for purposes of providing and improving our services. Clients or account holders who opt in to our services agree to this per this policy.

Some third-party sites accessed through our site will also track your browsing activities when they serve you content. If you are visiting such sites, your browser may allow you to set the DNT signal on your browser so that third parties (particularly advertisers) know you do not want to be tracked.

  6. CHANGES TO DATA PROTECTION POLICY

Cleantech Group may make changes to its Data Protection Policy at any time, and you will be notified if and when this occurs.

Date: May 11, 2018
